[
    {
        "question": "Which is the largest state in Australia by land area?",
        "answer": "Western Australia"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many states comprise Australia?",
        "answer": "Six"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many Federal territories are part of Australia?",
        "answer": "Ten"
    },
    {
        "question": "By land area, which is Australia`s largest territory?",
        "answer": "Australian Antarctic Territory"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state capital features a full-scale replica of the Parthenon?",
        "answer": "Nashville"
    },
    {
        "question": "What body of water separates Australia and New Zealand?",
        "answer": "Tasman Sea"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state capital is known as the `City in a Forest`?",
        "answer": "Atlanta"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is Bohemian Switzerland National Park?",
        "answer": "Czech Republic"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which continent is home to the only egg-laying mammals in the world?",
        "answer": "Australia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why is the Bronx called the Bronx?",
        "answer": "After a landowner named Jonas Bronck"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lusaka is the capital of which African country?",
        "answer": "Zambia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country borders Zambia to the north?",
        "answer": "Congo"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country borders Zambia to the west?",
        "answer": "Angola"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country borders Zambia to the east?",
        "answer": "Malawi"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can you find the world`s largest naturally frozen ice rink?",
        "answer": "Canada"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which lake crosses the borders of Vermont, New York, and Canada?",
        "answer": "Lake Champlain"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country has the largest forest found within a city?",
        "answer": "Brazil"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which U.S. state is closest to the Tropic of Cancer?",
        "answer": "Hawaii"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two oceans are connected by the Drake Passage?",
        "answer": "Atlantic and Pacific"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the Archipelago Sea?",
        "answer": "Finland"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can you find the Cathedral of St. Basil the Blessed?",
        "answer": "Moscow"
    },
    {
        "question": "What London landmark is protected by six ravens?",
        "answer": "Tower of London"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which island was once named the `Island of the Pelicans`?",
        "answer": "Alcatraz Island"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Griffith Observatory is located where?",
        "answer": "Los Angeles"
    },
    {
        "question": "`Blucifer` is the nickname for which city`s iconic horse statue?",
        "answer": "Denver"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is Africa`s westernmost point?",
        "answer": "Cape Verde"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can you find the hottest temperatures in California?",
        "answer": "Mojave Desert -- Specifically Death Valley, which is located in Mojave Desert."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the lowest elevation point in California?",
        "answer": "Death Valley -- 282 feet below sea level"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where does California`s Highway One travel?",
        "answer": "Along the Pacific coast -- It is also known as Highway 101 and Pacific Coast Highway"
    },
    {
        "question": "Coney Island is located in which New York City burrough?",
        "answer": "Brooklyn"
    },
    {
        "question": "What island has Australia`s tallest mountain?",
        "answer": "Heard Island"
    },
    {
        "question": "What U.S. national park is nicknamed `the American Spa`?",
        "answer": "Hot Springs National Park, Arkansas"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Po River is the longest river in which country?",
        "answer": "Italy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country serves as the home of the largest farm in the world?",
        "answer": "The Mudanjiang City Mega Farm is located in China and takes up almost 23 million acres."
    },
    {
        "question": "Frankenmuth, a U.S. city nicknamed `Little Bavaria`, is located in what state?",
        "answer": "Michigan (It is a German-style town in Saginaw County. It is well known for its hotels and old-style German buildings.)"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Caribbean island is known as `Little England`?",
        "answer": "Barbados -- Judging by the colonial architecture, the proclivity for gardens and cricket, it seems fitting."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country (and it`s territories) cover the most time zones?",
        "answer": "France and its eight territories cover 12 time zones."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what country are April Fool`s jokes climaxed with the saying `Doroughe sizdah`?",
        "answer": "Iran"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of the Democratic Republic of Congo?",
        "answer": "Kinshasa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which continent would you find the Amur River in?",
        "answer": "Asia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US state includes the telephone area code 501?",
        "answer": "Arkansas"
    },
    {
        "question": "What seaport`s name is Spanish for `white house`?",
        "answer": "Casablanca"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the city of Tobruk located?",
        "answer": "Libya"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why is \u00c5land known as the `Islands of Peace`?",
        "answer": "No military has entered it since Finnish takeover"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of Monaco`s four quarters is best known for casinos?",
        "answer": "Monte Carlo"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many stars appear on the Australian flag?",
        "answer": "Six"
    },
    {
        "question": "What`s the principal river of Ireland?",
        "answer": "Shannon"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Central African Republic?",
        "answer": "Bangui"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bengui is the capital of which land-locked country?",
        "answer": "Central African Republic"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country borders Central African Republic to the north?",
        "answer": "Chad"
    }
]